Hamas is not a resistance group. It's a terrorist organization.
And this is exactly why Aaron Parnes.
It's hard to trust Aaron Parnes because, I mean, this guy has his own hidden agenda.
He's pushing propaganda that is fed to him by the Democratic establishment, the ruling class and the Republican Party.
Hamas is not a terrorist group. It's a resistance group.
Because if you take a look at it, Palestinians have always lived under Israeli occupation, blockade and settler colonialism for decades.
The white supremacist apartheid state of Israel that is backed by billions from the United States government and from the military have stole their land,
kicked them out of their homes and turned Gaza into a prison.
Basically, October 7 wasn't a random attack that came out of nowhere.
It was a desperate breakout from the system after years of daily humiliation, killings and the genocide that Israel was inflicting on Palestinians.
Resistance fighters always hit back against their oppressors however they can.
Israel is the one with the massive army, with United States made bombs in the Iron Dome.
They've been bombing, starving and sniping Palestinians for generations.
The real cause of all of this mass death is the Israeli government and the United States government.
You can't blame Hamas for fighting back because if you were being oppressed, starved and killed every day,
I hope you'd have the same urge to fight back for your freedom.